<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="cpo_website_news_list_1" model="cpo_news_list">
            <!--<field name="cpo_layer_photo" type="base64" file="website_cpo_advertising/static/src/images/layerimg/layer_1_2.jpg"/>-->
            <field name="sequence">2</field>
            <field name="cpo_new_title">What is a PCB?</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_date'>2019-01-20</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_editor'>Charlie</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_content'>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>
                        PCB (Printed Circuit Board), the Chinese name for printed circuit boards, also known as printed circuit boards,
                        is an important electronic component, a support for electronic components, and a carrier for electrical
                        connection of electronic components. Because it is made by electronic printing, it is called a "printing" circuit board.
                    </p>
                    <img src="/website_cpo_advertising/static/src/images/layerimg/layer_1_2.jpg" />
                    <p>
                        After the electronic equipment adopts the printed board, due to the consistency of the same printed board,
                        the manual wiring is avoided, and the electronic components can be automatically inserted or mounted,
                        automatically soldered, and automatically detected to ensure the quality of the electronic equipment. ,
                         Increased labor productivity, reduced costs, and ease of maintenance.
                    </p>
                ]]>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="cpo_website_news_list_2" model="cpo_news_list">
            <!--<field name="cpo_layer_photo" type="base64" file="website_cpo_advertising/static/src/images/layerimg/layer_1_2.jpg"/>-->
            <field name="sequence">1</field>
            <field name="cpo_new_title">What is a PCBA?</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_date'>2019-01-23</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_editor'>Charlie</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_content'>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>
                        PCBA is the abbreviation of Printed Circuit Board +Assembly in English, which means that the PCB blank board
                        passes through the SMT upper part, and then passes through the whole process of DIP plug-in, referred to as PCBA.
                        This is a commonly used method in the country, and the standard way of writing in Europe and America is PCB'A,
                        plus "'", which is called the official idiom.
                    </p>
                    <img src="/website_cpo_sale/static/src/images/pcba_1.jpg"/>
                    <p>
                        Printed circuit boards, also known as printed circuit boards, printed circuit boards, often use the English
                        abbreviation PCB (Printed circuit board), is an important electronic component, is the support of electronic
                        components, It is the provider of the circuit connection of electronic components. Because it is made using
                        electronic printing technology, it is called a "printing" circuit board.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Prior to the advent of printed circuit boards, the interconnection between electronic components relied on
                        wires to form a complete line.
                    </p>
                ]]>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="cpo_website_news_list_3" model="cpo_news_list">
            <!--<field name="cpo_layer_photo" type="base64" file="website_cpo_advertising/static/src/images/layerimg/layer_1_2.jpg"/>-->
            <field name="sequence">3</field>
            <field name="cpo_new_title">What is a PCBA?</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_date'>2019-01-22</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_editor'>Charlie</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_content'>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>
                        SMT is a surface mount technology (short for Surface Mount Technology) called surface mount or surface mount
                        technology. It is currently the most popular technology and process in the electronics assembly industry.
                    </p>
                    <img src="/website_cpo_sale/static/src/images/smt_1.jpg.jpg"/>
                    <p>
                        It is a surface or other substrate surface on which a leadless or short lead surface mount component (SMC/SMD,
                        Chinese called a chip component) is mounted on a printed circuit board (PCB). In the above, the circuit
                        assembly technology is assembled by soldering or dip soldering.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Since the beginning of the 21st century, China's electronic information products manufacturing industry has
                        grown at a rate of more than 20% per year, and its scale has ranked second in the world for three consecutive
                        years since 2004. Driven by the rapid development of China's electronic information industry, China's surface
                        mount technology (SMT) and production lines have also developed rapidly. The key equipment for surface mount
                        production lines, the automatic placement machine, has been among the best in the world.
                    </p>
                ]]>
            </field>
        </record>
        <record id="cpo_website_news_list_4" model="cpo_news_list">
            <!--<field name="cpo_layer_photo" type="base64" file="website_cpo_advertising/static/src/images/layerimg/layer_1_2.jpg"/>-->
            <field name="sequence">4</field>
            <field name="cpo_new_title">Why do you have to deal with the special surface of the PCB?</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_date'>2019-01-22</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_editor'>Charlie</field>
            <field name='cpo_new_content'>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p>
                        SMT is a surface mount technology (short for Surface Mount Technology) called surface mount or surface mount
                        technology. It is currently the most popular technology and process in the electronics assembly industry.
                    </p>
                    <img src="/website_cpo_sale/static/src/images/smt_1.jpg"/>
                    <p>
                        It is a surface or other substrate surface on which a leadless or short lead surface mount component (SMC/SMD,
                        Chinese called a chip component) is mounted on a printed circuit board (PCB). In the above, the circuit
                        assembly technology is assembled by soldering or dip soldering.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        Since the beginning of the 21st century, China's electronic information products manufacturing industry has
                        grown at a rate of more than 20% per year, and its scale has ranked second in the world for three consecutive
                        years since 2004. Driven by the rapid development of China's electronic information industry, China's surface
                        mount technology (SMT) and production lines have also developed rapidly. The key equipment for surface mount
                        production lines, the automatic placement machine, has been among the best in the world.
                    </p>
                ]]>
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>