<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="assets_frontend_temrs" inherit_id="website.assets_frontend" name="Temrs Conditions">
        <xpath expr="." position="inside">
            <link rel="stylesheet" href="/website_cpo_sale/static/src/css/cpo_service.css"/>
        </xpath>
        <xpath expr="//script[last()]" position="after">
            <script type="text/javascript" src="/website_cpo_sale/static/src/js/cpo_service.js"></script>
        </xpath>
    </template>

    <template id="cpo_web_service" name="Terms &amp; Conditions">
        <!--<t t-call="web.layout">-->
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <!--<t t-set="additional_title">Service</t>-->
            <section class="jumbotron s_big_message oe_img_bg oe_custom_bg cpo_service_box" style="background-image: url('/website_cpo_sale/static/src/images/banner_1.jpg');">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="row" style="color:#FFFFFF;">
                        <div class="col-md-8 mt64 mb64 bg-black-25">
                            <h2 class="o_default_snippet_text">Terms &amp; Conditions!</h2>
                            <p class="o_default_snippet_text">General terms and conditions of sale</p>
                            <!--<a class="btn btn-warning btn-lg o_default_snippet_text" href="/en_US/page/website.contactus">联系我们</a>-->
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <!--<section id="banner_bg" class="s_text_block_image_fw oe_img_bg">-->
                <!--<div class="container">-->
                    <!--<div class="col-md-8 mt64 mb64 bg-black-25">-->
                        <!--<h2 class="o_default_snippet_text">PCB &amp; PCBA &#45;&#45; One Stop Service</h2>-->
                        <!--<h4 class="o_default_snippet_text">Chinapcbone Technology Limited</h4>-->
                    <!--</div>-->
                <!--</div>-->
            <!--</section>-->
            <h2 class="text-center" id="cpo_terms_title">Terms &amp; Conditions</h2>
            <section class="s_three_columns">
                <div class="container">
                    <div class="row" id="cpo_temrs_conditions">
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE</h4>
                            <p>
                                The present General Terms and Conditions of Sale (GT&amp;CS) are subject to change. The current version
                                is the one appearing on our website www.icloudfactory.com: GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF SALE.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                In the absence of any special written agreements, the placement of an order by the Customer indicate
                                acceptance of the GT&amp;CS herein.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                They prevail, according to the provisions of the article L. 441-6 of the Commercial Code, on all purchase
                                conditions, unless special sale conditions were written in agreement with both parties.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>AND CONDITIONS OF SALE</h4>
                            <p>
                                The present General Terms and Conditions of Sale (GT&amp;CS) are subject to change.
                                The current version is the one appearing on our website www.icloudfactory.com: GENERAL TERMS
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                All contractual agreements entered into will be between ChinaPCBOne Group and business clients
                                (herein referred to as “the Client”) who must be 18 years of age and legally competent.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                If ChinaPCBOne Group should unintentionally enter into a contractual agreement with a person legally
                                incapable to enter contracts, any contractual agreement between the two parties becomes void with immediate effect.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                Placing an order on www.icloudfactory.com requires the Client to register/set up an ChinaPCBOne online account (i.e. user profile).
                                Clients must register under their own name and complete all mandatory fields correctly.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>ACCOUNT OPENING</h4>
                            <p>
                                For any company account opening, the customer must provide to ChinaPCBOne Group his company name, the contact name, his department,
                                his contact information (address, telephone number, Fax, ...) as well as his VAT number and / or his SIRET number (France only).
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>PRICE</h4>
                            <p>
                                The current prices are those appearing on the offer written to the client.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>ORDERS</h4>
                            <p>
                                We provide an acknowledgement of order from the moment that the order is confirmed by our technical service,
                                and we inform the client in case of product unavailability, deferred delivery, …
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>DELIVERY</h4>
                            <p>
                                We provide an acknowledgement of order from the moment that the order is confirmed by our technical service,
                                and we inform the client in case of product unavailability, deferred delivery, …
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>GUARANTEE</h4>
                            <p>
                                Liability is only limited to merchandise supplied by ChinaPCBOne Group and does not apply to damage,
                                injury or loss of income coming from a defective component.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                Goods sold are guaranteed against any faulty operation due to a defect in material, defect
                                in the fabrication or conception, for a period of 3 months as from the date of invoice,
                                subject to a conform use of the product.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                Thus, the guarantee is excluded if the defect results from a modification of the product,
                                neglect or lack of maintenance of it by the user.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>LIMITATION OF THE GUARANTEE</h4>
                            <p>
                                Our guarantee is limited to repair or replacement of printed circuits PROVIDED BY ChinaPCBOne
                                Group recognized as defective by our technical service. The guarantee does not extend to
                                the repair time, transformation or change of equipment.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>DELAY, RETURNS, CLAIMS, CONTESTING</h4>
                            <p>
                                The customer must ensure at the time of delivery, in the presence of the carrier,
                                that the packages do not hold any trace of suffering, debris, burglary and that
                                the number of packages corresponds to the one stated on the shipping documents.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                The customer must mention the reserves on shipping documents, otherwise he must
                                notify it, according to the article L. 133-3 of the Commercial Code, to the
                                carrier by registered letter with recorded delivery at the latest within
                                three days after the delivery, with a copy sent to ChinaPCBOne Group. Otherwise,
                                no claims can be accepted by ChinaPCBOne Group.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                The printed circuit boards (PCB) must be returned with the delivery note or
                                the corresponding invoice, within maximum 5 days from the reception.
                                The returned printed circuit board (PCB) will be subject to a quality control before any decision-making.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>RETENTION OF TITLE AND TRANSFER OF RISK</h4>
                            <p>
                                Under the article 2367 and following ones of the Civil Code, the sold goods remain
                                the property of ChinaPCBOne Group until the full payment of the price and its accessories
                                (property clauses). In case of dispute or contesting from the customer, no compensation of any kind,
                                cannot call into question the title retention clause.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                This layout shall not interfere with the transfer to the customer as early as after the delivery,
                                risk of loss and damage of sold goods, as well as the damage they could cause.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>PROTECTION AND USE OF DATA</h4>
                            <p>
                                In order to ensure the best service for our customers, ChinaPCBOne Group and its partners
                                use some information provided by customers and only for a professional reason.
                                By adhering to the general terms and conditions of sale, the customer agrees to this so-called use.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                According to the Data Protection Act of 6 July 1978, you have a right of access and rectification of the data.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                According to the LCEN law, the online registration allows ChinaPCBOne Group to collect the permission to
                                receive emails. If the addresses are provided by the traditional trade channel, a commercial
                                message is sent to the client in order to confirm the use of his address. The relevance of
                                messages sending by ChinaPCBOne Group is based on information collected during the user
                                registration or at the interview with our sales force members.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4> FORCE MAJEURE</h4>
                            <p>
                                ChinaPCBOne Group should in no way be held responsible for delay or execution failure of its obligations
                                in case of force majeure, in particular in cases of natural disaster, bad weather,
                                fire, explosion, flood, national strike, accident, riot or civil disorder, abnormal
                                delay due to supplier, shortages of goods and material.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>CANCELLATION CLAUSE</h4>
                            <p>
                                In case of breach of contract by either party, this contract is automatically committed of right
                                in favor of the other party, without prejudice to damages and interests which may be claimed
                                from the defaulting party. The resolution takes effect 10 days after a sending formal
                                remained unsuccessful.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="cpo_temrs_content">
                            <h4>COMPETENCE ASSIGNATION</h4>
                            <p>
                                All disputes arising out of sales transactions subject to these GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS
                                OF SALE depend on the exclusive jurisdiction of the Commercial Court of Hauts de Seine (92).
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </section>
            <!--<section id="cpo_terms_and_conditions">-->
                <!--<div class="row">-->
                    <!--<div class="container">-->
                        <!--<a class="btn btn-primary" id="cpo_accept_temrs_conditions">Accept</a>-->
                    <!--</div>-->
                <!--</div>-->
            <!--</section>-->
        </t>
        <!--</t>-->
    </template>
</odoo>